<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steve Houël</title>
    <link>https://www.steve-houel.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Steve Houël</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.steve-houel.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.steve-houel.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steve-houel.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a #AWS #All9 certified Cloud Architect at Ippon Technologies. My field of expertise is DevOps &amp;amp; Cloud-based technologies and more specifically Serverless architectures. Speaker at events, contributor to OSS projects like JHipster or daSWAG and writer of blog articles or white papers &amp;ldquo;Serverless architectures, from theory to practice&amp;rdquo; in my spare time. You should have understood that, I love technology #CloudAddict
Certifications Experience Senior Cloud Architect - Global Technical Leader - Ippon Technologies Since February 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Events</title>
      <link>https://www.steve-houel.com/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steve-houel.com/events/</guid>
      <description> 2019  May 9 - Bordeaux - Observability pillars applied to Serverless May 14 - Nantes - To be or not to be Serverless May 21 - Toulouse - Observability pillars applied to Serverless May 23 - Lille - To be or not to be Serverless May 29 - Paris - Observability pillars applied to Serverless June 11 - Lyon - Observability pillars applied to Serverless June 19 - Lille - Serverless &amp;amp; security, what you need to understand  2018  March 15 - Lyon - Kit de survie d&amp;rsquo;une application Serverless March 28 - Nantes - To be or not to be Serverless March 29 - Toulouse - Kit de survie d&amp;rsquo;une application Serverless April 20 - Devoxx Paris - Kit de survie d&amp;rsquo;une application Serverless  2017  June 27 - Lyon - To be or not to be Serverless  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My OSS Projects &amp; Contributions</title>
      <link>https://www.steve-houel.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steve-houel.com/projects/</guid>
      <description> JHipster Dev Team
Open Source application generator for creating Spring Boot + Angular/React projects in seconds!
Website - Github
daSWAG Creator
Generate your full Serverless Web Application in seconds with daswag cli
Website - Github
and more on my Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.steve-houel.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.steve-houel.com/publications/</guid>
      <description> Articles  Les architectures Serverless Comment faire du Serverless L&amp;rsquo;observabilité appliqué au Serverless  WhitePaper  Les architectures Serverless v1 - De la théorie à la pratique Les architectures Serverless v2 - De la théorie à la pratique  Magazine  Programmez.com - 230 Programmez.com - 231  Video  To be or not to be Serverless Observability applied to Serverless - AWS Meetup Bordeaux Observability applied to Serverless - Ippon &amp;amp; Datadog Instant conseil  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>